Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-thai-chau-nh32-23816329 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Project Planning English

Nguyen Thai Chau Nh32

HR management at Bioseed

Vietnam

Summary

OBJECTIVE

Short term: In next five years, to become Senior Recruitment Specialist in Human

resources management; apply knowledge form Economic of University HCMC to

upgrade progress in HRM in organization which corporate with foreign company.

Long term: become specialist Human resources by developing Human resources framework which following by new method.

Experience

Bioseed

HR management

October 2015 - Present (9 years 6 months)

Vietnam

Bioseed Vietnam
Quality Assurance Officer
October 2015 - Present (9 years 6 months)
Tay Ninh

Bioseed Vietnam Limited
Quality Assurance Officer
October 2015 - Present (9 years 6 months)
Tay Ninh Province

Following up the activities of Plant processing & GOT (grow out testing).

- Following up the drying procedure; seed treatment and packing seed.
- Following up the fumigation for whole seed lot.
- · Perform GOT after harvest season.
- Following up and arrangement seed lots in storage rooms and warehouse.
- Make report for accounting department all lots in warehouse every month.

- # Seed testing as TCVN 8548: 2011.
- Seed sampling & dividing seed for seed testing.
- Determine and analyst the purity; inner matter; moisture content; other seed, P1000 seed weight and germination test.
- Take evaluation for seedling in germination test.
- Doing soil test & vigour test on demand.
- Periodically, checking the quality of seed lot at storage room.
- # Field inspection as TCVN 8550: 2011.
- To inspect the Isolation all areas of corn production in Winter-Spring season.
- To inspect other varieties of crop.
- Field inspection such as to cut tassel on male corn in pollination stage; male chopping before harvest.
- Check quality in the field, input stage in time.

agricultue agronomist March 2011 - Present (14 years 1 month)

VIET MA RUBBER COMPANY LIMITED

Human resource staff October 2013 - October 2014 (1 year 1 month) Ho Chi Minh City

Compensation:

- To prepare contract of employees
- Follow up annual leaves monthly and yearly.
- Complete monthly payment for employees.
- Follow up probation time of staff and inform line managers for evaluation.
- Ensure that company information is updated in Notice Board

Benefits:

- Following the sickness leave, maternity leave.
- Other insurance benefits for employees every month upon case-by-case.
- Update staffs list & payroll of all staffs to do Insurances.

Recruitment:

- Plan and matching candidates for position.
- Set up interview for recruitment.
- Inform the result of interview for candidates.
- · Saving CVs on HR system.

SOUTHERN SEED JOINT STOCK CORPORATION Quality control/Quality assurance staff.

March 2011 - October 2013 (2 years 8 months)

Ho Chi Minh City

IN LABORATORY:

- To analyze the seed sample such as: Corn, hybrid rice, and bean. The standards of testing include: Purity, moisture content, P1000 weight, germination and other variety testing (hybrid rice).
- To perform germination by vigor test and "Tetrazolium" method for imported seed lots.

IN THE PLANT

- # To take sampling in drying corn seed procedure and packing seed.
- # To check the quality of seed in cool storage and make report all seed lots in storage rooms.
- Checking equipments in factory periodically.

FIELD INSPECTION:

- To organize workshops with local government to train farmers for seed production in Highland, Cu Chi and Tay Ninh Province.
- To inspect hybrid corn production: Isolation, cutting tassel in pollination stage, male cutting and harvest (LVN 10, MX 10...)
- To inspect hybrid rice at Daklak provinces: Isolation, pollination, harvesting and open trial hybrid rice HR 182 in Long My province.

Education

Truòng Dai hoc Kinh Tê Thanh Pho Hô Chí Minh Bachelor's degree, Human Resources Management/Personnel Administration, General · (2015 - 2017)

Truòng Dai hoc Nông Làm Thành phó Hô Chí Minh Bachelor's degree, Agricultural Economics (2006 - 2010)